BU Records: President Emeritus' Office (Abner Vernon McCall), Inclusive: 1857-1995, undated, Bulk: 1985-1995
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- External, 1985-1995; 2
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (TSNL) (3 of 13), 1987-1995 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (TSNL) (4 of 13), 1987-1995 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (TSNL) (5 of 13), 1987-1995 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (TSNL) (6 of 13), 1987-1995 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (TSNL) (7 of 13), 1987-1995 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (TSNL) (8 of 13), 1987-1995 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (TSNL) (9 of 13), 1987-1995 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (TSNL) (10 of 13), 1987-1995 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (TSNL) (11 of 13), 1987-1995 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (TSNL) (12 of 13), 1987-1995 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (TSNL) (13 of 13), 1987-1995 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Texas Utilities Company, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Waco Business League, 1985-1989 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Waco Philosophers Club, 1986-1988 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Well Way Centers, Incorporated (1 of 3), 1985-1988 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Well Way Centers, Incorporated (2 of 3), 1985-1988 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Well Way Centers, Incorporated (3 of 3), 1985-1988 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Volunteer Services Council, 1984-1986, undated (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Waco Baptist Academy, 1987-1988 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- People, 1969-1990; 3
  This series includes correspondence and their supporting documents. The series is organized alphabetically by last name. Some materials are dated to McCall's time as President of Baylor, but were housed with other materials from his time as President Emeritus and kept in that original order during processing. This series is in good condition.
  - Allbritton, Joe, 1985-1990 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Baugh, John F., 1986 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Dawson, Matt, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - McCall, Frances Bortle, 1969-1988 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Reynolds, Herbert H. (1 of 2), 1981-1990 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Reynolds, Herbert H. (2 of 2), 1981-1990 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Watson, Allan, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Personal, 1958-1995; 4
  This series includes McCall's appointment books, honorary degrees and awards, personal correspondence, and speeches. Some materials are dated to McCall's time as President of Baylor, but were housed with other materials from his time as President Emeritus and kept in that original order during processing. McCall's 1985 appointment book from his first seven months as President Emeritus is in BU Records: Chancellor's Office (Abner Vernon McCall). This series is in good condition.
  - Appointment Book, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Appointment Book, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Appointment Book, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Appointment Book, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Appointment Book, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Appointment Book, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Appointment Book, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Appointment Book, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Appointment Book, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Appointment Book, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Biographical Information, 1981-1990 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Honorary Degrees and Awards, 1936-1983 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Resolutions in Appreciation of the Services of Abner V. McCall, Texas Power and Light Company, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Retirement Letters, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Speeches (1 of 3), 1958-1990, undated (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Speeches (2 of 3), 1958-1990, undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Speeches (3 of 3), 1958-1990, undated (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Speeches — Baptists, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Speeches — General, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Speeches — Tributes, 1986-1988, undated (Box 40, Folder 8)